Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dean's records, 1968-2003; Series 11
  - Samuel Hoi records, 1989-2000; Series 11 subseries 6
    - Memorandum to the Art School Committee concerning the general situation and the activities of the faculty, 1984 May 21; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/ Proposal for Grivenances, 1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/Information for Faculty, 1992; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/Information for Faculty, 1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/Information for Faculty, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Manual, 1982; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Employment Information/Tips/Readings, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Higher Education Executive Associates Inc. Faculty Handbook Seminar, 1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Memphis College of Art Faculty Handbook, 1988; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Minneapolis College of Art & Design, 1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Oregon Art Institute/Pacific Northwest College of Art Faculty Handbook, 1990-1991; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco Art Institute Faculty Manual & Personnel Policy Statement, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - On Sammy's Calendar, 1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Staff Meetings, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Chairs Council, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Museum School Collaboration, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Administrative Mentor Program Susan's, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Studio 405 OD/CE Catalog Production, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Academic Calendar, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Old Faculty Lists, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Address list & phone numbers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - AAA Travel Agency: Travel Arranger Handbook, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Course Evaluations - Background, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - New Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - CSA Courses/Labs Information (Schedules/Evaluations/Faculty), 1988-1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Swain Report, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Academic Studies Dept. Syllabi, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Academic Studies, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - ESL English as a Second Language, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Elderhostel, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence file: T, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence file: U, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence file: V, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence file: W, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence file: X-Y-Z, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Annmarie Garden Calvery County, Maryland, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Artwork, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Advertising Schedules, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - City Paper, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Washington Post, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Kids & Teen, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Washington Times, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Open Program Advertising, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - OP/CE Catalog, 1996 Summer; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Cadmus Magazines, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Open Program Info, 1995-1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Parent & Child magazine, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Washington Parent, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Families Newspaper, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Flyers, Brochure, Etc., circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Free Publicity Arts Events Calendars, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Public Service Announcements, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - WETA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - WLTT/94.7 FM, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Program Curriculm Outcomes (Rona's Subcommittee), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Ceramic Course, 1996 Spring; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Architectural Workshop Evaluations I, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Computer Graphics Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Computer Lab, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Computer Graphics (OP), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Computer Graphics BFA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Interior Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Landscape Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - OP Paint/Draw, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Fine Arts Department, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Class Syllabi William Willis, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Fine Arts Retreat, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - The Foundations Program, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Fine Arts Electives, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Drawing, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Foundations, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - IRMA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Graphic Design (Faculty, Studentst, General Information, Misc.), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Graphic Design BFA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Graphic Design (O.P.), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Photography BFA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Photography (O.P.), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Printmaking, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Sculpture, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Open Sculpture Competition, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Summer- Ceramics Devers, 1991; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Courses Information, 1988-1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - I.R.M.A, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Drawing, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Courses Information (Foundations Dept, IRMA, Fine Arts Elective), 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Academic Studies Syllabi, 1989 Fall; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Graphic Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Hubert Leckie Scholarship, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Graphic Design Courses, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Photo - Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Children's Workshop, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - College Board of Overseers, 2000 May 1; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - College Board of Overseers, 2000 February 14; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - College Board of Overseers, 1999 November 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - College Board of Overseers, 1999 September 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1999 April 28; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1999 February 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1998 November 18; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1998 September 23; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1998 April 30; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Short Range Facilities Committee, 1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Development Comittee School Board of Overseers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Nominations School Board of Overseers, 1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Facilities Committee School Board of Overseers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Student Life Committee School Board of Overseers, 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Educational Policy Committee Board of Overseers, 1996-1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - New Building Study Board of Overseers Facilities Committee, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Nominating Committee School Board of Overseers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Arthur Cotton Moore Drawing & Painting, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - School Board of Overseers Correspondence, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Quick Survey School Board of Overseers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Educational Policy Committee School Board of Overseers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - School Board of Overseers Meeting, 1998 February 18; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - School Board of Overseers Meeting, 1997 November 12; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1997 September 10; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1997 April 30; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - School Board of Overseers Meeting, 1997 February 19; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - School Board of Overseers Meeting, 1996 November 16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - School Board of Overseers Meeting, 1996 September 12; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1996 May 15; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1996 February 28; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1995 November 15; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1995 September 20; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1995 April 26; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1995 April 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1994 November 16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1994 September 21; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Meeting of the Board of Overseers Corcoran School of Art, 1994 April 20; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1994 February 23; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1993 November 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1993 September 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1993 April 7; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1993 February 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1992 November 18; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Academic Studies Department, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Artist Citizenship, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - AAS Program, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - AOL agreement, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Computer Graphics Dept., circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Association, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Resources Plan, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Fine Arts Dept, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Foundation Dept, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Graphic Design Dept, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Hochschule d. Kunste - Exchange CSA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Library, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Marketing Study, 1998; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Structural Additions CGA, 1998; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Photography Departments, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - College Staff Retreats, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Student Tuition, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - WPA/C, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Restricted Accounts (Scholarships), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - DCAD: Comparative Report of Applicants by Major, 1998-2000; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - DCAD Strategic Planning Retreat II, 1999; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - DCAC: A Creative Partnership of the Corcoran School of Art & Pratt Institute, 1999; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - DCAD: Report to Management, 1998 October; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Delaware College of Art and Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Corcoran Feedback on Proposeed DCAD Curriculur Revision, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - DCAD Reports of Visits, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - DCAD Board of Directors, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - DCAD Financials, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - DCAD Board Members, Admin, Faculty, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - DCAD Publications, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Wilmington, 2000; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Draft: A Proposal for the Delaware of College of Art in Wilmington, Delaware, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - DCAD Board of Overseers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - DCAD Admissions, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Arts Summit Delaware Division of the Arts, 1995 November 4; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - AAS Program, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Initial Application To Confer Academic and Honorary Degrees- Private Colleges and Universities Located in Delaware, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Policies, Standards and Procedures for Approving Degree Granting Institutions of Higher Education, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - DCAD Jt. Venture Document, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - DCAD Organizational Chart & Floor Plans, 1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - DCAD Misc. Documents, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 75, Folders 22-23)
    - DC Public Schools Arts & Humanities Initiative, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Samuel Hoi, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Expansion Arts National Endownment for the Arts, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Children's Studio School, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - DC Project, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - The Levine School of Music, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - American University, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - George Washington University, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Art in Public Places Chinatown Metrorail Station Project, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Duke Ellington School, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Menus, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Fine Arts, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Arts for the Aging, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Arts for the Aging Corcoran Work/Study Program Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Art from the Heart, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - A. Salon, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Capital Children's Museum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Promotions Steve SzAbu, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Crossing Over Consortium, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Ellipse Arts Center Arlington County VA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Greater Reston Arts Center, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - McLean Project for the Arts MPA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Viriginia Center for the Creative Arts, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Annmarie Garden, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Academy of the Arts, Easton, Maryland, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Rockville Arts Place, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Washington Area Arts Consortium, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Washington Cultural Alliance, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Washington Research Library Consortium, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Noche Crist, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Safe Kids Coalition, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Very Special Arts, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - WPA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - The University of Maryland, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Washington Center for Photography, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Washington Review, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Washington Sculpture Group, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Georgetown Arts Commission, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Junior Citizens Corps. Inc. Washington DC, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Museum & Arts Washington, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Cultural Allaince of Greater Washington, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Pyrmaid Atlantic, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - DC Consortium, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - DC Service Corps, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - AIA The American Institute of Architects, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - DC Artists/Organizations, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - Kirk Pillow records, 1994-2001; Series 11 subseries 7
    Contains records of Kirk E. Pillow, Dean of the Corcoran School from August 2008-2011. Materials include correspondence, course files, research files, dating from 1994-2001.
    - Pillow - Vitae, circa 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Pillow statement, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Pillow - Form & Content, 1994; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Pillow - Habituating Madness..., 1997; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Pillow - Comment..., 1999; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Pillow - Jupiter's Eagle, 2001; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Pillow - Versions & Forgeries, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Pillow - Goodman's Distinction, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Pillow - Phil IIOW (Intro), 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Pillow - Phil 203 (Modern), 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Pillow - Phil 240 (Logic), 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Pillow - Phil 305 (Phil & Lit), 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Pillow - Phil 333 (Phil of Art), 2001; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Pillow - Phil 355 (Contemporary), 2001; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Pillow - Phil 431 (Kant), 2001; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Handbook of Phil and Lit Project, 2001; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Goodman LeWitt, Final Draft, 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Goodman LeWitt, Sent to JAAC, circa 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 18)
    - Goodman LeWitt, Draft Comments, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 19)
    - Goodman LeWitt, Sent to LeWitt, 2003; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 20)
    - Goodman LeWitt at ASA, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 21)
    - Course Descriptions & Rubics, circa 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - HAS Metaphor, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 23)
    - LeWitt Project, 1996; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 24)
    - Lens Flare, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 25)
    - Does Goodman's Distinction, 2003; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Hegel & Homosexuality, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 27)
    - JAAC Kivy Response, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 28)
    - Emerson Grant & Phil & Lit Submission, 2002; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 29)
    - Goodman Revision - JAAC, 2003; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 30)
    - NEH Summer Stipend, 1999; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 31)
    - Kirk Pillow x 4188, 1999; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 32)
    - Hegel Legacy Comment, circa 2000; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 33)
    - Pillow Hegel's Hysterical Sublime, 1991; Series 11 subseries 7 (Box 170, Folder 34)